
 ~@~@~@~@~@~@~@~@~ START OF ERRORLOG FOR 2021-09-14 ~@~@~@~@~@~@~@~@~Loaded global params ::
SCREEN_W :: 1024
SCREEN_H :: 768
CURSOR_VISIBLE :: True
RESTRICT_SCREEN :: True
AUTOSHAPING :: True
TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE :: 10
STIMULI_COLORS :: normal
HOST_CONNECTED :: True
RFID_READER_CONNECTED :: False
DRO_DURATION :: 1
REWARD_TYPE :: pellet
REWARD_AMOUNT :: 1
DEBUG_WINDOW_ON :: True
Loaded monkey params
{'H049': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/31/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450491', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450193', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H055': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/3/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452575', 'Right Wrist': '989001040454104', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H033': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/24/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450302', 'Right Wrist': '989001040448586', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J860': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '5/23/1997', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449144', 'Right Wrist': '982092062453171', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J989': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/28/1999', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453548', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453248', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '3-183': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/25/2003', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452877', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452708', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '4-238': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '10/14/2004', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450034', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453872', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '5-113': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/16/2005', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452751', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452833', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '7-225': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '9/25/2007', 'Left Wrist': '989001040448686', 'Right Wrist': '989001040453884', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J719': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/23/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453493', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453944', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J939': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/13/1998', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452818', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452985', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '4-148': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '6/17/2004', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450413', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450997', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H063': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/10/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449539', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450376', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H415': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/15/2001', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449519', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450346', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '3-091': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/22/2003', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454057', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452646', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J729': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/31/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062448789', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453231', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '10-017': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/15/2010', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454179', 'Right Wrist': '989001040454133', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '14-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/7/2014', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454243', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450437', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '6-088': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '6/9/2006', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449975', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450228', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '9-105': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/28/2009', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454073', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452926', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J743': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/12/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453264', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450799', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '10-193': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '10/12/2010', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450336', 'Right Wrist': '989001040453816', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '12-073': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/26/2012', 'Left Wrist': '989001040448604', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452684', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J436': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '4/11/1993', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450307', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450322', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '5-201': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '8/18/2005', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450024', 'Right Wrist': '989001040454437', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J721': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/27/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453391', 'Right Wrist': '982091062454058', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '11-163': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/15/2011', 'Left Wrist': '989001040448789', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452722', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '13-014': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '3/4/2013', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452509', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453818', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J857': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/5/1998', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453851', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450119', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '13-029': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/14/2013', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450315', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452929', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '5-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/26/2005', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452499', 'Right Wrist': '989001040449555', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '8-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/15/2008', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450215', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452707', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H425': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '10/4/2001', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453197', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450328', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J487': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/15/1994', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453263', 'Right Wrist': '982091062454072', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J904': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '2/15/1998', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450465', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453657', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'FISH1': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '989002009125723', 'Right Wrist': '989002009112544', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'FISH2': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '989002009229212', 'Right Wrist': '0', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'MICHELE1': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '989001039039939', 'Right Wrist': '989001039039961', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'MICHELE2': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '982091065413918', 'Right Wrist': '982091065413935', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'GROUP': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '999999999999999', 'Right Wrist': '', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}}

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/ACTS/ACTS/ACTS_frontend.py", line 391, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/ACTS/ACTS/ACTS_frontend.py", line 255, in main
    if self.mutable_text == self.m_params[key]['Left Wrist']:
AttributeError: 'FrontEnd' object has no attribute 'mutable_text'

Loaded global params ::
SCREEN_W :: 1024
SCREEN_H :: 768
CURSOR_VISIBLE :: True
RESTRICT_SCREEN :: True
AUTOSHAPING :: True
TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE :: 10
STIMULI_COLORS :: normal
HOST_CONNECTED :: True
RFID_READER_CONNECTED :: False
DRO_DURATION :: 1
REWARD_TYPE :: pellet
REWARD_AMOUNT :: 1
DEBUG_WINDOW_ON :: True
Loaded monkey params
{'H049': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/31/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450491', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450193', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H055': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/3/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452575', 'Right Wrist': '989001040454104', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H033': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/24/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450302', 'Right Wrist': '989001040448586', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J860': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '5/23/1997', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449144', 'Right Wrist': '982092062453171', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J989': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/28/1999', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453548', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453248', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '3-183': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/25/2003', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452877', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452708', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '4-238': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '10/14/2004', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450034', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453872', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '5-113': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/16/2005', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452751', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452833', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '7-225': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '9/25/2007', 'Left Wrist': '989001040448686', 'Right Wrist': '989001040453884', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J719': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/23/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453493', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453944', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J939': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/13/1998', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452818', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452985', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '4-148': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '6/17/2004', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450413', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450997', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H063': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/10/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449539', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450376', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H415': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/15/2001', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449519', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450346', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '3-091': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/22/2003', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454057', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452646', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J729': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/31/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062448789', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453231', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '10-017': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/15/2010', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454179', 'Right Wrist': '989001040454133', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '14-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/7/2014', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454243', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450437', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '6-088': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '6/9/2006', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449975', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450228', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '9-105': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/28/2009', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454073', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452926', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J743': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/12/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453264', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450799', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '10-193': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '10/12/2010', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450336', 'Right Wrist': '989001040453816', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '12-073': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/26/2012', 'Left Wrist': '989001040448604', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452684', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J436': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '4/11/1993', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450307', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450322', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '5-201': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '8/18/2005', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450024', 'Right Wrist': '989001040454437', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J721': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/27/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453391', 'Right Wrist': '982091062454058', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '11-163': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/15/2011', 'Left Wrist': '989001040448789', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452722', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '13-014': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '3/4/2013', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452509', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453818', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J857': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/5/1998', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453851', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450119', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '13-029': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/14/2013', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450315', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452929', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '5-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/26/2005', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452499', 'Right Wrist': '989001040449555', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '8-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/15/2008', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450215', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452707', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H425': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '10/4/2001', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453197', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450328', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J487': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/15/1994', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453263', 'Right Wrist': '982091062454072', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J904': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '2/15/1998', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450465', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453657', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'FISH1': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '989002009125723', 'Right Wrist': '989002009112544', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'FISH2': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '989002009229212', 'Right Wrist': '0', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'MICHELE1': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '989001039039939', 'Right Wrist': '989001039039961', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'MICHELE2': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '982091065413918', 'Right Wrist': '982091065413935', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'GROUP': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '999999999999999', 'Right Wrist': '', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}}
User quit the program

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/ACTS/ACTS/ACTS_frontend.py", line 397, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/ACTS/ACTS/ACTS_frontend.py", line 308, in main
    check_quit(event=event)
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\ACTS\ACTS\_modules\pgtools.py", line 142, in check_quit
    raise SystemExit
SystemExit

Loaded global params ::
SCREEN_W :: 1024
SCREEN_H :: 768
CURSOR_VISIBLE :: True
RESTRICT_SCREEN :: True
AUTOSHAPING :: True
TIME_TO_AUTOSHAPE :: 10
STIMULI_COLORS :: normal
HOST_CONNECTED :: True
RFID_READER_CONNECTED :: False
DRO_DURATION :: 1
REWARD_TYPE :: pellet
REWARD_AMOUNT :: 1
DEBUG_WINDOW_ON :: True
Loaded monkey params
{'H049': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/31/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450491', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450193', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H055': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/3/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452575', 'Right Wrist': '989001040454104', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H033': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/24/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450302', 'Right Wrist': '989001040448586', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J860': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '5/23/1997', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449144', 'Right Wrist': '982092062453171', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J989': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/28/1999', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453548', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453248', 'Room': '507.01', 'PiSystem': '103', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '3-183': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/25/2003', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452877', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452708', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '4-238': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '10/14/2004', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450034', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453872', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '5-113': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/16/2005', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452751', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452833', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '7-225': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '9/25/2007', 'Left Wrist': '989001040448686', 'Right Wrist': '989001040453884', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J719': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/23/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453493', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453944', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J939': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/13/1998', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452818', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452985', 'Room': '507.02', 'PiSystem': '102', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '4-148': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '6/17/2004', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450413', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450997', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H063': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/10/1999', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449539', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450376', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H415': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/15/2001', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449519', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450346', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '3-091': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/22/2003', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454057', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452646', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J729': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/31/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062448789', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453231', 'Room': '507.03', 'PiSystem': '105', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '10-017': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/15/2010', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454179', 'Right Wrist': '989001040454133', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '14-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '6/7/2014', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454243', 'Right Wrist': '989001040450437', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '6-088': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '6/9/2006', 'Left Wrist': '989001040449975', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450228', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '9-105': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/28/2009', 'Left Wrist': '989001040454073', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452926', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J743': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/12/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453264', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450799', 'Room': '507.04', 'PiSystem': '104', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '10-193': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '10/12/2010', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450336', 'Right Wrist': '989001040453816', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '12-073': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/26/2012', 'Left Wrist': '989001040448604', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452684', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J436': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '4/11/1993', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450307', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450322', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '5-201': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '8/18/2005', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450024', 'Right Wrist': '989001040454437', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J721': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '3/27/1997', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453391', 'Right Wrist': '982091062454058', 'Room': '507.05', 'PiSystem': '106', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '11-163': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '7/15/2011', 'Left Wrist': '989001040448789', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452722', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '13-014': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '3/4/2013', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452509', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453818', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J857': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/5/1998', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453851', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450119', 'Room': '507.06', 'PiSystem': '107', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '13-029': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '4/14/2013', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450315', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452929', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '5-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/26/2005', 'Left Wrist': '989001040452499', 'Right Wrist': '989001040449555', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, '8-069': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/15/2008', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450215', 'Right Wrist': '989001040452707', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'H425': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '10/4/2001', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453197', 'Right Wrist': '982091062450328', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J487': {'Sex': 'F', 'DOB': '5/15/1994', 'Left Wrist': '982091062453263', 'Right Wrist': '982091062454072', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'J904': {'Sex': 'M', 'DOB': '2/15/1998', 'Left Wrist': '989001040450465', 'Right Wrist': '982091062453657', 'Room': '507.07', 'PiSystem': '109 & 110', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'FISH1': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '989002009125723', 'Right Wrist': '989002009112544', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'FISH2': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '989002009229212', 'Right Wrist': '0', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'MICHELE1': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '989001039039939', 'Right Wrist': '989001039039961', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'MICHELE2': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '982091065413918', 'Right Wrist': '982091065413935', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}, 'GROUP': {'Sex': 'NA', 'DOB': 'NA', 'Left Wrist': '999999999999999', 'Right Wrist': '', 'Room': 'NA', 'PiSystem': 'NA', 'task-order': 'SHAPE1-SHAPE2-TwoChoice-MTS-MTSseq1-MTSseq3-MTSseq5', 'ITI': '5000', 'Timeout': '15000', 'SHAPE1_to_decrement': '3', 'SHAPE1_to_increment': '3', 'SHAPE1trials': '100', 'SHAPE1criterion': '85', 'SHAPE2size': '200', 'SHAPE2_zones': 'TRUE', 'SHAPE2trials': '100', 'SHAPE2criterion': '85', '2choicesize': '200', '2choicereset': '60', '2choiceproblems': '100', '2choicetrials': '10', '2choicecorrect': '8', 'MTSsize': '200', 'MTStrials': '100', 'MTScriterion': '85', 'MTSseqsize': '200', 'MTSseqtrials': '30', 'MTSseqcriterion': '26'}}
pellet
pellet
User quit the program

Traceback (most recent call last):
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/ACTS/ACTS/ACTS_frontend.py", line 397, in <module>
    frontend.main()
  File "C:/Users/YLab/Downloads/ww_programs/ACTS/ACTS/ACTS_frontend.py", line 308, in main
    check_quit(event=event)
  File "C:\Users\YLab\Downloads\ww_programs\ACTS\ACTS\_modules\pgtools.py", line 142, in check_quit
    raise SystemExit
SystemExit

